const quizQuestions1en = [{
    question:"The electrode in MMA welding (SMAW) is:",
    answers: ["a consumable coated electrode;",
    "a non-consumable electrode;",
    "a continuous electrode;",
    "a bare electrode."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"What type of current and polarity should be used to weld with a recently purchased basic electrode?",
    answers: ["Direct current, electrode connected to the negative pole, as it is a usual connection configuration for these types of electrodes.",
    "Direct current, electrode connected to the positive pole, as it is a usual connection configuration for these types of electrodes.",
    "Alternating current as it is a usual current type for this sort of electrodes.",
    "As indicated by the manufacturer on the box/package containing the electrodes."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"The joining of plates can be done by:",
    answers: ["rivets, screws and casting;",
    "screws, welding and straightening;",
    "rivets, screws and welding;",
    "welding, gluing and tracing."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"What is the heat source used for welding with coated electrodes?",
    answers: ["Electrical resistance.",
    "Electric arc.",
    "Oxyacetylene Flame.",
    "Electric flame."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"What is the heat source used for oxy-acetylene welding?",
    answers: ["Electrical resistance.",
    "Electric arc.",
    "Oxyacetylene Flame.",
    "Electric flame."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"This is an advantage of welding:",
    answers: ["No specialized labour is needed (anyone can weld);",
    "It is the fastest method of joining metal parts;",
    "The welded joint is not permanent and can be easily disassembled;",
    "Normally, welded joints are free from defects."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"This is an advantage of welding:",
    answers: ["No specialized labour is needed (anyone can weld);",
    "Less joint weight compared to other joining methods;",
    "The welded joint is not permanent and can be easily disassembled;",
    "Normally, welded joints are free from defects."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"This is an advantage of welding:",
    answers: ["No specialized labour is needed (anyone can weld);",
    "It is the most suitable joining method for the most used metal, namely carbon steel;",
    "The welded joint is not permanent and can be easily disassembled;",
    "Normally, welded joints are free from defects."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"This is a limitation of welding:",
    answers: ["The welded joint remains very hot for a long time;",
    "It is difficult to protect against arc light, which is very intense;",
    "Sometimes you need to use PPE;",
    "If the welder makes a mistake, it is difficult to repair a defective welded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"\"This is a \"\"disadvantage\"\" of welding with coated electrodes (for the success of weekend works):\"",
    answers: ["The welded joint remains very hot for a long time;",
    "It is difficult to protect against arc light, which is very intense;",
    "Sometimes you need to use PPE;",
    "If working at the customer's home, the coated electrodes will usually run out before the service is finished."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"This is a limitation of welding:",
    answers: ["The welded joint remains very hot for a long time;",
    "It is difficult to protect against arc light, which is very intense;",
    "Sometimes you need to use PPE;",
    "To ensure an adequate quality, laborious preparatory actions (cleaning, assembling, ...) are necessary."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"Which of the following gases is flammable?",
    answers: ["CO2.",
    "CO.",
    "Air.",
    "Acetylene."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"In the case of coated electrode welding, if the electrode is sticking to the part, you should:",
    answers: ["replace the electrode with a thicker one;",
    "change the welding power source;",
    "increase the welding current;",
    "increase the travel speed."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"How do you find out that the power source, to be used for covered electrode welding, is one of the direct current types?",
    answers: ["Such a machine is usually larger in size than a welding transformer.",
    "\"Such a machine has the markings \"\"+\"\" and \"\"-\"\" near terminals.\"",
    "\"Such a machine is marked \"\"~\"\" near the terminal for the electrode holder connection.\"",
    "Such a machine always has a fan for cooling the bridge rectifier."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"Some coated electrodes have the core tips marked in different colours. What is the purpose of such color electrode identification?",
    answers: ["There is a Standard that prescribes this identification of electrodes in colour for the welder to avoid possible mistakes when choosing an electrode of the particular type that is out of its packaging.",
    "It does not mean anything for the welder, as it refers to an internal control of the electrode fabricator.",
    "\"It helps in identification of used electrodes (they have a darker colour, that is, they do be \"\"burned\"\").\"",
    "In this way, the electrode manufacturer helps the welder to avoid possible mistakes when choosing a particular electrode that is out of its packaging."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"In the case of coated electrode welding, if you do not use PPE, the risk of suffering an electric shock would be higher:",
    answers: ["during welding, i.e., during the open arc period (as the welding current is normally high, above 100 A).",
    "when the power source is already on, but the arc is not yet open (as the open circuit voltage of the power source can be rather high).",
    "at the moment of striking the arc, because the current grows a lot at this moment.",
    "when the electrode is very hot, because at this moment its coating loses its insulating properties."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"If, in the case of welding with coated electrode, your weld was far to be perfect, the most likely cause of this was:",
    answers: ["the electrode;",
    "the power source;",
    "the base metal;",
    "myself."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"The welding ...",
    answers: ["is a process of joining materials;",
    "is a process of joining, as well as cutting, materials;",
    "is a process of heat treatment of materials;",
    "is a manufacturing process that can join, cut and heat-treat materials."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"A welded joint ... ",
    answers: ["can be disassembled (just heat it up again until the melting point of the joint metal);",
    "can be disassembled (but only before the joint metal solidifies);",
    "is permanent (to disassemble it, a cutting process should be applied);",
    "is permanent (if a welder makes mistakes, the welded part will have to be discarded, there is no way to recover it);"],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"\"Welding with coated electrodes is the most used by \"\"weekend welders\"\", because ...\"",
    answers: ["it is much easier to master compared to other welding processes, for example, MIG/MAG (GMAW);",
    "even without a proper preparation of the welder, the weld always comes out with quality, which depends only on the coated electrode used;",
    "just choose a quality coated electrode and the weld will always come out with quality as well;",
    "there is a good availability of MMA/SMAW power sources and coated electrodes in tool shops and the investment is low."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"\"If one of your friends asks you to weld/repair a metal joint in his house, before accepting the \"\"service\"\", one of your questions will be ...\"",
    answers: ["whether water will be available to cool the joint after it has been welded?",
    "whether will there be a gas stove to dry the electrodes?",
    "what is the chemical composition of the material to be welded?",
    "whether there will be the availability of electricity?"],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"What is the unit of measurement of electrical voltage?",
    answers: ["Volt",
    "Ampere",
    "Ohm",
    "Hertz"],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"What is the unit of measurement of electrical resistance?",
    answers: ["Volt",
    "Ampere",
    "Ohm",
    "Hertz"],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"0" 
    },
     {
    question:"What is the unit of measurement of the electric current?",
    answers: ["Volt",
    "Ampere",
    "Ohm",
    "Hertz"],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"0"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of these materials is non-ferrous?",
    answers: ["Stainless steel.",
    "Copper.",
    "Carbon steel.",
    "Cast iron."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Which of these materials is non-ferrous?",
    answers: ["Stainless steel.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Carbon steel.",
    "Cast iron."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Aluminium is:",
    answers: ["a ferrous metal;",
    "a composite material;",
    "a non-ferrous metal;",
    "a very light steel grade."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Copper is:",
    answers: ["a ferrous metal;",
    "a composite material;",
    "a non-ferrous metal;",
    "an alloy of the bronze."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Copper is:",
    answers: ["a ferrous metal;",
    "a composite material;",
    "a non-ferrous metal;",
    "an alloy of the brass."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Carbon steel is:",
    answers: ["a ferrous metal;",
    "a composite material;",
    "a non-ferrous metal;",
    "an alloy of the cast iron."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Stainless steel is:",
    answers: ["a ferrous metal;",
    "a composite material;",
    "a non-ferrous metal;",
    "an alloy of the white cast iron."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Cast iron is:",
    answers: ["a ferrous metal;",
    "a composite material;",
    "a non-ferrous metal;",
    "a high hardness steel."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Metals, unlike non-metals, ...",
    answers: ["are solid;",
    "have a higher melting point;",
    "are harder;",
    "are good electrical conductors."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Metals, unlike non-metals, ...",
    answers: ["are solid;",
    "have a higher melting point;",
    "are harder;",
    "are good thermal conductors."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Non-metals, unlike metals, ...",
    answers: ["are liquid;",
    "have a lower melting point;",
    "are less hard;",
    "are good electrical insulators."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Non-metals, unlike metals, ...",
    answers: ["are liquid;",
    "have a lower melting point;",
    "are less hard;",
    "are good thermal insulators."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"Metals, unlike non-metals, ...",
    answers: ["are solid;",
    "have a higher melting point;",
    "are harder;",
    "have usually higher thermal expansion (e.g., compared to ceramics)."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"What is the temperature measurement unit?",
    answers: ["Joule.",
    "Degree.",
    "Cal.",
    "Watt."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"A material that returns to its original shape after deformation is:",
    answers: ["elastic.",
    "plastic.",
    "resistant.",
    "tough."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"If you heat these materials with an oxy-acetylene torch, which one will be melted first?",
    answers: ["Copper.",
    "Aluminium.",
    "Carbon steel.",
    "Cast iron."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"\"If one of your friends asks you to weld/repair a metal joint in his house, before accepting the \"\"service\"\" you will ask him ...\"",
    answers: ["whether water will be available to cool the joint after it has been welded?",
    "whether there will be a gas stove to dry the electrodes?",
    "what is the chemical composition of the material to be welded?",
    "what kind of material to be welded?"],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"\"If one of your friends asks you to weld/repair a metal joint in his house, before accepting the \"\"service\"\" you will ask him ...\"",
    answers: ["whether water will be available to cool the joint after it has been welded?",
    "whether there will be a gas stove to dry the electrodes?",
    "what is the chemical composition of the material to be welded?",
    "how thick is the metal?"],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"If one of your friends asks you to weld/repair a white coloured metal joint at his house, you will think that this is more likely ...",
    answers: ["copper;",
    "stainless steel;",
    "white cast iron;",
    "carbon steel."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"If one of your friends asks you to weld/repair a white coloured metal joint at his house, you will think that this is more likely ...",
    answers: ["copper;",
    "aluminium;",
    "white cast iron;",
    "carbon steel."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"1"
    },
    {
    question:"If one of your friends (also a weekend welder) thinks about accepting the service of fixing an aluminium pan, your suggestion will be ...",
    answers: ["for him to look for electrodes with a white coating;",
    "for him to look for electrodes for stainless steels that can also be used to weld aluminium;",
    "for him to look for electrodes for non-ferrous, for example copper, which can also be used to weld aluminium;",
    "although there are electrodes for welding aluminium, but he shouldn't even think to accept such a service!"],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"1"},
    {
    question:"An 87.5 mm sheet was ground by 12.4 mm. What is the final thickness of the sheet?",
    answers: ["75,1 mm.",
    "71,5 mm.",
    "57,1 mm.",
    "85,1 mm."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"To ensure the highest possible mechanical strength of a joint of 3 - 4 mm thick carbon steel sheets welded with covered electrodes, you will ...",
    answers: ["deposit 1 or 2 (if welding on both sides) welds without any reinforcement;",
    "deposit 1 or 2 (if welding on both sides) welds with a slight reinforcement (1 - 2 mm) on both the weld face and the root;",
    "deposit 1 or 2 (if welding on both sides) welds with good reinforcement (up to 5 mm) both on the face and on the root;",
    "follow the rule: the more you deposit, the better, that is, the greater the reinforcement, the greater the mechanical strength of the weld."],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, which type of joint offers the highest mechanical strength for the same thickness of sheets?",
    answers: ["Welded.",
    "Riveted.",
    "Bolted (with large, high-strength screws).",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, which type of joint will be the lightest for the same mechanical strength and sheet thickness?",
    answers: ["Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Welded.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, what type of joint is prone to sudden collapse with no noticeable signs of imminent failure?",
    answers: ["Welded.",
    "Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"2"
    },
    {
    question:"You have to perform a weld of 1.5 meters in length. How many covered electrodes will you need if each electrode can give a 0.3 m weld?",
    answers: ["2",
    "4",
    "7",
    "5"],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"A MIG/MAG welder was welding for 14 minutes without stopping at a travel speed of 8 cm/min. What is the length of the resulted weld?",
    answers: ["112,00 m",
    "1,12 m",
    "6,72 m",
    "2 ,12 m"],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"A MIG/MAG welder was welding for 14 minutes without stopping at a travel speed of 6 cm/min. What is the length of the resulted weld?",
    answers: ["0,84 m",
    "0,92 m",
    "1,00 m",
    "1,20 m"],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"You have to make four welds of 60 cm; 30 cm; 20 cm and 90 cm. What will be the total length of the welds?",
    answers: ["1,0 m",
    "1,6 m",
    "1,8 m",
    "2,0 m"],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"Is it necessary to use leather gloves when welding with covered electrodes?",
    answers: ["Yes, it is necessary to avoid electric shock or burns when touching the workpieces.",
    "Yes, it is necessary but only for the hand holding the electrode holder (to avoid electric shock).",
    "Yes, it is necessary but only for the free hand (which does not hold the electrode holder), to avoid electric shock or burns when touching the workpieces.",
    "It is not necessary as the electrode coating is dielectric and the electrode holder is also coated with an electrical insulator."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"When removing slag, the eyes shall be protected:",
    answers: ["Turning the head aside;",
    "Closing the eyes;",
    "Using goggles with side shields;",
    "Directing the slag particles outwards."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"Is it necessary to use a welding mask when welding with covered electrodes?",
    answers: ["Yes, it is necessary.",
    "Not necessary when making short welds (of the tack type), just close your eyes when striking the arc.",
    "Not necessary when making short welds (of the tack type), as its main function is to protect the skin against radiation from the arc if the latter is open for a long time.",
    "It is not necessary."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"When welding with covered electrodes, is it necessary to use protective transparent goggles if you already use a welding mask?",
    answers: ["It is unnecessary, as the welding mask offers much better protection.",
    "Yes, especially if the welding mask has a broken light filter lens.",
    "It is necessary, especially when removing slag and spatter, as well as performing or assisting other operations.",
    "It is unnecessary if the welder works alone, so there is no danger that someone is carrying out a risky operation nearby (grinding, turning, etc.)."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"You need to make some welds of different lengths, starting by the shortest and ending by the longest. What is the correct sequence of welds in increasing length order?",
    answers: ["0.45 m; 20 cm; 7 cm; 1.05 m; 56 mm",
    "56 mm; 7 cm; 200 mm; 0.45 m; 1.05 m",
    "5 cm; 7 cm; 56 mm; 0.45 m; 1.05 m",
    "0.45 m; 200 mm; 7 cm; 56 mm; 1.05 m"],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"You need to make some welds of different lengths, starting by the longest and ending by the shortest. What is the correct sequence of welds in decreasing length order?",
    answers: ["0.45 m; 20 cm; 7 cm; 1.05 m; 56 mm",
    "1.05 m; 0.45 m; 200 mm; 7 cm; 56 mm",
    "5 cm; 7 cm; 56 mm; 0.45 m; 1.05 m",
    "0.45 m; 200 mm; 7 cm; 56 mm; 1.05 m"],
    correctAnswer:"1",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"When welding with covered electrodes, the weld quality depends mainly on:",
    answers: ["the welder;",
    "the covered electrode;",
    "the welding power source;",
    "the workpiece to be welded."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"Electrical shock can become a problem, with arc welding if:",
    answers: ["the welding leads are too large;",
    "the welding leads are too long;",
    "welding leads are coiled up on hangers;",
    "electrical connections are not insulated."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, which type of joint will need less time for its execution for the same mechanical strength and sheet thickness?",
    answers: ["Welded.",
    "Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, which type of joint will be the cheapest in its execution for the same mechanical strength and sheet thickness?",
    answers: ["Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Welded.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, the realization of which type of joint demands deeper and more diversified knowledge?",
    answers: ["Welded.",
    "Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, the realization of which type of joint demands a longer prior training?",
    answers: ["Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Welded.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, the realization of which type of joint is accompanied by an increased risk of generating joint defects?",
    answers: ["Welded.",
    "Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, which type of joint is characterized by the greatest number of possible joint defects?",
    answers: ["Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Welded.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, during the realization of which type of joint there is a greater risk of suffering burns?",
    answers: ["Welded.",
    "Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"0",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, during the realization of which type of joint it is necessary to wear safety glasses?",
    answers: ["Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Welded.",
    "Of all types of joints."],
    correctAnswer:"3",
    subject:"3"
    },
    {
    question:"What do you think, which type of joint will be the most difficult to be disassembled (for the same mechanical strength and sheet thickness)?",
    answers: ["Riveted.",
    "Bolted.",
    "Welded.",
    "Adhesive bonded joint."],
    correctAnswer:"2",
    subject:"3"}
];